Edward G. Ramberg Papers 1916-1994 Mss.Ms.Coll.88
American Philosophical Society
- Series III. RCA, 1927-1973; 1.0 Linear feet
  - "Statistical Theory of Thermoelctric, Galvano- And Thermomagnetic Phenomena in Metals" Reviews of Modern Physics, 3, No. 1: 1-42., 1931; Frank, N.H.; Sommerfeld, Arnold, 1868-1951 (Box 8)
  - "Über das Elektronenmikroskop" Zeiss-Nachrichten Heft 9: 1-6., 1935; Scherzer, Otto; Sommerfeld, Arnold, 1868-1951 (Box 8)
  - "Über den Photoeffekt in der K-Schale der Atome, insbesondre über die Voreilung der Photoelektron" Annalen der Physik 5 Folge Bd 4, Nr. 4: 409-449., 1930; Schur, G.; Sommerfeld, Arnold, 1868-1951 (Box 8)
  - "Studies of the Semiconducting Properties of the Compound CsAu" Physical Review 115, no. 1: 57-62., 1959; Sommer, Alfred; Spicer, W.E.; White, J.G. (Box 8)
  - "Electronic Spectroscopy", n.d.; Schroeder, Alfred C.; Sziklai, George C. (Box 8)
    Includes photos of equipment
  - "Principles of Color Selection in a Light Valve Color T.V. Projector" Proceedings of 1971 International Symposium of Society for Information Display, Philadelphia, PA, Incomplete., Good, William E.; True, Thomas T. (Box 8)
  - "A Holographic Communication Theory with Applications to Holographic Digital Storage", 1969; Vilkomerson, David H.R. (Box 9)
  - 1946, Wilson, E.W. (Box 9)
    To V.K. Zworykin
  - "Applications of the Electron Microscope in Metallurgy" Metals Technology: American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers Technical Publication no. 1594: 1-25., 1943; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "Electron Microscopy in Chemistry" Electronics., 1943; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "Electron Optical Systems and Their Applications:" Journal of the Institution of Electrical Engineers 79, No. 475: 1-10., 1936; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "Facsimile Picture Transmission" Proceedings of the Institute of Radio Engineers 17 No 3: 536-550., 1929; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper article, 1962; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - Photocells and their application, 1947; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - Television Patents, n.d.; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "A Compact High Resolving Power Electron Microscope" Journal of Applied Physics 14, No. 12: 658-673., 1943; Hillier, James; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "An Electron Microscope for Practical Laboratory Service" AIEE Committee on Communication., 1941; Hillier, James; Vance, A. W.; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "Kerr Cell Method of Recording Sound" Transactions of the Society of Motion Picture Engineers 12, No. 35: 748-756., 1928; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982; Zworykin, V. K.; Lynn; and Hanna (Box 9)
  - "The Secondary Emission Multiplier-A New Electronic Device" Proceedings of the Institute of Radio Engineers 24, No. 3: 351-375., 1936; Malter, L.; Morton, George Ashmun, 1903-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - Electron Optics and the Electron Microscope--Folder 1, 1945; Hillier, James; Morton, George Ashmun, 1903-; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Vance, A. W.; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - Electron Optics and the Electron Microscope--Folder 2, 1945; Hillier, James; Morton, George Ashmun, 1903-; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Vance, A. W.; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "Applications de la Microscopie Electronique et de la Diffraction Electronique a la Metallurgie" Centenaire de l'Association des Ingenieurs sortis de l'Ecole de Liege (a.I.L.g): 29-40., 1947; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - "Photoelectric Cells" Encyclopedia of Chemical Technology Volume 10 Pentacene to Polymethine Dyes: 519-542., 1953; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 9)
  - PhotoElectricity and Its Application, 1949; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 10)
  - "Standards Conversion of Television Signals" Electronics: 86-91., 1952; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 10)
  - "Surface Studies with the Electron Microscope" Journal of Applied Physics 12, No. 9: 692-695., 1941; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 10)
  - "Television its Indebtedness and Contributions to Science", Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907-; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 10)
  - "The Caesium-Magnesium Photocell" Journal of the Optical Society of America and Review of Scientific Instruments, 19, No.2: 81-89., 1929; Wilson, E.D.; Zworykin, V. K., (Vladimir Kosma), 1889-1982 (Box 10)
  - 1960, Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - 1961, Unidentified author (Box 10)
    German correspondence
  - Aviation Math and Physics Curriculum for Teaching, 1972-1973; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Bibliography of Scientific Books in German, 1958; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Bomb Test Suit, 1962-1964; Unidentified author (Box 10)
    Materials relating to a lawsuit that Ramberg joined, in which 186 plaintiffs from 22 countries attempted to sue the U.S. and USSR to limit the proliferation of nuclear weapons. There is correspondence from Francis Heisler and Ralph B. Atkinson, attorneys in the case, and a brief history of the suit from its beginnings with Linus Pauling in 1958.
  - "Colour Television Encyclopedia Entry" Encyclopaedic Dictionary of Physics Supplementary Volume 1., n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - David Sarnoff Golden Anniversary, 1956; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Degrouping in Color Kinescopes and Its Correction: The Apparent Beam Pattern in the Deflection Plane", Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Der Photo Effekt", n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Direct View Color Kinescopes-A Series of 11 Papers by Engineers of Research Department, RCA Laboratories Division And of Tube Department, RCA Victor Division" Proceedings of the IRE: 1177-1263., 1951; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Efficiency Considerations in Thermoelectric Cooling and Power Generation", Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Eisenach, 1961; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Electron Optics of Focusing Masks in Tri-Color Kinescopes", 1953; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Focusing-Grill Kinescopes" RCA Laboratories Report LB-1026: 1-19., 1956; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - "Fortschritte im Gebiet der Photoemission", n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - General Electric Cell Information, 1946; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - IEEE David Sarnoff Award given to Edward G. Ramberg, 1972; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Patents and Sony Research, Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Permission to publish reprints, 1948; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Photoelectric Cells (Bibliography), (1943?); Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Phototubes, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 10)
    Photographs
  - Phototubes/Photoelectric Cells, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Princeton Authors, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - Proceedings of the IRE, 42, no. I., 1954; Unidentified author (Box 10)
  - RCA Laboratories Annual Dinner, 1956-1965; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - RCA Pamphlets, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - RCA Scientific Equipment, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - "Recent Developments in Photo- and Thermoelectricity, particularly with Regard to their Applications", Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - "Sekundareffekte in der lichtelektrichen Leitung", Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - "Semiconductor Thermoelectric Generators and Refrigerators and Their Applications" Russian Literature Survey Infosearch London., 1956; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - Television Research Patents, 1969; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - Television Textbook, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - Television Tube Patents, 1965; Unidentified author (Box 11)
  - Twenty-Five Years at RCA Laboratories, 1942-1967, 1968; Unidentified author (Box 11)
- Series IV. Society for Social Responsibility in Science, 1947-1974; 0.5 Linear feet
  The Series on the Society for Social Responsibility in Science (SSRS) contains material on its founding in 1948, including a folder on a conference held at Haverford College. There is correspondence relating to Wolfgang Losch, a German scientist who toured the United States in 1968, and material from the Nominating Committee of the SSRS from 1969, which includes biographical sketches of possible members and correspondence. There is a list of members and a constitution from 1967, Council Meeting minutes and constitutions from 1956, 1959, and 1960, a list of officers from 1960, and a constitution from 1952. In the Victor Patchkis file is his analysis and history of the organization after its first ten years.
  - 1947-1974, 27 items; Bechert, Karl, 1901-1981 (Box 12)
    Correspondence German
  - 1973, Committee on Social Implications of Technology. (Box 12)
  - 1972, 1973, 2 items; Deubners (?) (Box 12)
  - "Scientific Considerations for the Human Conscience", 1956; Flanders, Ralph E. (Box 12)
    Given at the SSRS Conference at Swarthmore College
  - 1950, 1959, 6 items; Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Box 12)
  - 1972, 3 items; Hersh, Phyllis (Box 12)
  - 1948, 2 items; Jehle, Herbert (Box 12)
  - 1968, 49 items; Losch, Wolfang (Box 12)
  - 1969, 1970, 51 items; Luck, Werner (Box 12)
  - 1969, 1970, 6 items; Muller, (?) (Box 12)
  - 1971, 2 items; Muller, Julia (Box 12)
  - 1960, Patchkis, Victor (Box 12)
  - Conference Against the Spread of Nuclear Weapons, Oslo Norway, 1961; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 12)
  - "Does the Scientist have a Special Social Responsibility?" Paper given at the Congress of Scientists on Survival, 1964; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 12)
  - Mice, Men and Fallout, 1956, 1958; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 12)
  - "Problems and Priorities" SPARK Committee for Social Responsibility in Engineering 2, No. 2, 2-3., 1972; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 12)
  - Constitution, 1952; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Founding, 1948; 5 items; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Meetings, 1970; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Members and Constitution, 1967; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 1956; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 1959; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 1960; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Newsletter, 1949-1954; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Newsletter, 1955-1958; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Newsletter, 1959-1964; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Nominating Committee, Folder 1, 1969; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - Nominating Committee, Folder 2, 1969; Society for Social Responsibility in Science (ACT). (Box 12)
  - 1954, 2 items; Stewart, Albert (Box 12)
  - "Science and the Business of Living", 1947; Vail, James G. (Box 12)
  - 1967, 4 items; Wergeland, H., (Harald), 1912-1987 (Box 12)
  - Civil Defense Essay, n.d.; Unidentified author (Box 12)
  - Conference of Scientists at Haverford College, 1948; Unidentified author (Box 12)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer article on Society for Social Responsibility in Science, 1960; Unidentified author (Box 12)
    Charter in Bucks County approval
  - SPARK Committee for Social Responsibility in Engineering, 5, No. 2., 1975; Unidentified author (Box 12)
- Series V. Peace concerns, 1961-1994; 1.5 Linear feet
  Ramberg was strongly opposed to America's involvement in the Vietnam War and the peace series contains material about the military industrial complex, pamphlets, and writings, including some by Ramberg and his wife on the war.
  The series includes material about the Southampton Monthly Meeting of the Society of Friends, of which Ramberg was a member -- mostly financial information from 1986-1992, when he served as treasurer -- and other miscellaneous information on Friends' Meetings in the early 1990's and on the Friends' Committee on National Legislation.
  - 1961, American Friends Service Committee. (Box 13)
  - Brochures, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Chemical Weapons- NARMIC: National Action/ Research on the Military Industrial Complex, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Citizens Concerned About Nuclear Power, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
  - Investing and Quakers, 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - Justice and Foreign Policy, Folder 1, 1975 (Box 13)
    Friends Peace Committee
  - Justice and Foreign Policy, Folder 2, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Justice and Foreign Policy, Folder 3, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
  - Justice and Foreign Policy, Folder 4, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
  - Military Industrial Complex and Vietnam, 1968-1972 (Box 13)
  - Nonviolence--1, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Nonviolence--2, 1968-1969 (Box 13)
  - Peace and Service-Bucks County, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Pollution--1, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Pollution--2, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Prosperity and Foreign Policy (Box 14)
  - Quakers and Social Action, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Quakers and Social Responsibility, 1968, 1970 (Box 14)
  - "Stewardship of Wealth Among Friends", 1984 (Box 14)
  - Voters for Peace, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - "Engineer and Military Technology", 1973; Ramberg. Edward G. (Box 14)
  - Letter to the Editor on Vietnam, 1967; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Letters to the Editor on Vietnam, 1968-1973; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Nuclear Concerns, 1975; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1960-1961; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1968; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1969; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1970; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1971; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1972; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1973; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1979; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1980; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Social Issues Correspondence with Government Officials, 1982-1985; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Statement on Conscription, 1979; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Tax Deductible Contributions to Peace Organizations, 1990; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 14)
  - Test Ban Campaign, 1972-1978; Ramberg, E. G., (Edward Granville), 1907- (Box 15)
    Against testing of nuclear weapons by the United States
  - Peace Committee, 1966-1973; Ramberg, Sarah Sargent (Box 15)
  - Peace and Service Newsletter, 1987; Society of Friends. Bucks (Pa.) Quarterly Meeting. (Box 15)
  - "Action Suggestions on Issues Concerning the United Nations", 1992; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - Committee of the United Nations, 1992, 1994; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - Minutes, 1986-1987; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - Minutes, 1990-1991; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - Minutes, 1992; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - Minutes, 1993; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - Minutes, 1994; Society of Friends. Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (Box 15)
  - 1986, Specter, Arlen (Box 15)
    Contra Aid
  - United Nations Peacekeeping Report, 1994; United Nations (Box 15)
  - "An Octogenarian Outing to Indians", 1973; Unidentified author (Box 15)
- Series VI. Amnesty International, 1975-1993; 4.0 Linear feet
  The Amnesty International Series consists primarily of material on various countries monitored by Amnesty International for violations of human rights, 1972-1994. Ramberg was a member of Bucks County Group Number 85 of Amnesty International, which "adopted" prisoners from Greece, Yugoslavia, Indonesia, and several African countries. Ramberg would write to the prisoner and to members of the United States government and their own government about their case. There is also information on Chile and Argentina during the era of "desaparecidos," and a substantial amount of information on Amnesty International campaigns against the death penalty in the United States and in other countries, including Ramberg's numerous letters of protest to governors of states that were conducting executions of prisoners.
  Part of the value of this series is in the detailed documentation it offers of the activities of a local chapter of Amnesty International. It contains the minutes of meetings of the Bucks County Group between 1975-1994, which give regular updates on adoption cases, copies of requests for financial assistance that were sent to members, and a wealth of correspondence with Deborah Margulies, president of the Bucks County Group. This series also includes Amnesty International news releases, updates on the situation in specific countries, and newspaper and magazine articles on countries in need. Finally, there is a letter from September 24, 1975, that details the early history of the Bucks County Group and Ramberg's involvement in it, along with pamphlets that explain the purpose of the Bucks County Group.
  - Adoption Groups, 1978-1981; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Adoptions and Country Information, 1989; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Adoptions Groups Policies, 1983; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Amnesty Action Newsletter-1, 1976-1979; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Amnesty Action Newsletter-2, 1981-1988; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Amnesty International Activities, 1977-1978; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Amnesty International Newsletter, 21, No. 9., 1991; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Argentina, 1980-1981; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Baltimore Meeting, 1981; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Brazil And Torture, 1990; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Campaign Against Prisoner Abuse, 1982; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Catalog of Gifts, 1987; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Change of Address Forms, n.d.; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Chile Information, 1982; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Czechoslovakia: Amnesty International Briefing, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Death Penalty, 1988; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Death Penalty in Bangladesh, 1985; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Death Penalty in France, 1981; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Death Penalty in the United States, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Delaware Meeting, 1982; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Disappearances, prisoner updates, n.d.; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - East European Coordination Group, 1979, 1985; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - El Salvador, 1982; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Ethiopia, 1985, 1986; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - European Conscientious Objectors, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - French Embassy Assignment, 1981; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Grenadian Prisoner--Adoptee, 1982, 1983; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Group Membership Update, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Guatemala, 1982; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Guidelines for Local Groups, 1985; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Haiti Campaign, 1985; Amnesty International (Box 16)
  - Handbook and Update, 1977, 1978; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Handbook for Groups, Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Human Rights: Death Penalty, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Human Right: Issues, 1976-1988; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Human Rights: Pamphlets, n.d.; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Human Rights: South Africa, 1977; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Human Rights: United Nations, 1978; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Indonesia, 1976-1981; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Indonesia -- Prisoners of Conscience, 1976; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Indonesia--"Women and Political Detention", 1976; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - International Women's Day, 1983; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Job Opportunity, 1982; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - London Staff Appointment, 1978; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Margulies, Deborah (speaking engagement), 1984; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Matchbox, 1981-1982; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Conference, 1979-1985; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1982-1984; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Monthly Memo, 1977; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Monthly Update, 1988; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Multiple Adoption Guidelines, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Netherlands Adoption Group, 1977-1978; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - New Philadelphia Group, 1983; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - News Releases, 1978-1979; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - News Releases, 1981-1983; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Newspaper articles, 1976; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Peru, 1979; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Petition to Leonid Brezhnev, n.d.; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Petition to Nicolae Ceausescu, n.d.; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Poland, 1981-1982; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Prisoners and the Death Penalty, 1983; Amnesty International (Box 17)
  - Recommendations for letters to Paraguay, Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Report to the Membership, 1980; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Staff Appointments, 1982, 1983; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Terrorism and South Africa, 1976; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Urgent Action Network, 1978-1985; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - USSR -- Death Penalty, 1984-1990; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Visit to Washington D.C., 1981; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Washington, DC Conference, 1978; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Writers and News Media Professionals "Disappeared", 1982; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Yugoslavia, 1983-1988; Amnesty International (Box 18)
  - Adoptions, 1978; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Adoption Group Evaluation Form, 1979; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Annual Appeal, 1977-1985; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Annual Group Report, 1985; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Annual Prisoner Report, 1979-1984; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Argentina, 1978-1981; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Budget Request, 1981; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Chile, 1981; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Contributions and Membership, 1976-1981; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Czech Prisoner, 1978-1980; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)
  - Ethiopia, 1978-1988; Amnesty International. Bucks County (Pa.) Group 85. (Box 18)